[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This red herbivorous mammal is endangered because of habitat loss and human interference.", "correct_answer": "Lesser Panda", "incorrect_answers": ["The Indian Red Badger", "The Red Fox", "The  Asian  Red  Squirrel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What mineral present in some mineral waters is used as a cure for different types of depression?", "correct_answer": "Lithium", "incorrect_answers": ["Copper", "Aluminium", "Vanadium"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The giant pandas diet is 99% this.", "correct_answer": "bamboo", "incorrect_answers": ["bananas", "fish", "honey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did Einstein pass away?", "correct_answer": "1955", "incorrect_answers": ["1960", "1954", "1956"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the name of the dish Pad see ew, very popular in Thailand and Laos?", "correct_answer": "Fried with soy sauce", "incorrect_answers": ["Noddles and meat", "Triple meal", "Hungry tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of a traditional German wheat beer glass?", "correct_answer": "Weizenbier glass", "incorrect_answers": ["Heifeweizenbier glass", "Weizenstarkbier glass", "Witbier glass"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mitochondrias function in cells is to perform this.", "correct_answer": "To convert organic materials into energy", "incorrect_answers": ["To control chemical reactions within the cytoplasm", "To store information needed for cellular division", "To process proteins targeted to the plasma membrane"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this horror movie Drew Barrymores character must answers horror based trivia questions.", "correct_answer": "Scream", "incorrect_answers": ["Are You Afraid of the Dark", "I Know What You Did Last Summer", "Campside Tails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Olympus Mons lies on Mars.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this classic gangster movie Arthur Cody Jarrett scales a gas storage tank and screams Made it Ma, top of the world.", "correct_answer": "White Heat", "incorrect_answers": ["The Big Sleep", "Little Caesar", "The Postman Always Rings Twice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Antarctic ozone hole reached one of its largest ever sizes in September 2000 when it was 11.5 million square miles (29,784,863 square km).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following native American groups of people speak a Southern Athabaskan language?", "correct_answer": "Apache", "incorrect_answers": ["Arawaks", "Alaskans", "Arizonans"]}]